<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sneha Mayya</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sneha Mayya</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 12:31:51 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chapter 1</title>
      <link>/2020/08/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 12:31:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/08/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;Welcome to Real-imination Tower! A game based off of the famous one and only platform for gaming- Roblox!! I will be the main host for today!&amp;rdquo; host Duce Brapples exclaimed into his mic. &amp;ldquo;Lets start with a bit of information about our competitor who is put to the test to complete 5 dangerous stages in the tower and be examined by a pro at this tower, a gamer who has played this before and has died multiple times and respawned!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sorry!</title>
      <link>/2020/08/sorry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2020 10:25:49 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/08/sorry/</guid>
      <description>Hey guys, I&amp;rsquo;m back and sorry for the inconvenience but I will be posting weekly now cause there is too much to write in one day so yeah. Now, Chapter Two of Ghosts will be postponed until next Monday! C&amp;rsquo;ya! Sorry bout this! ( A part of Chapter 1 WILL come out today!!) -Sneha 8/4/2020</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ghosts - Introduction</title>
      <link>/2020/08/ghosts-introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Aug 2020 10:46:14 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/08/ghosts-introduction/</guid>
      <description>Hi again and welcome back to day 2 of this blog! After some thinking, I decided to start off with something I&amp;rsquo;ve longed to write about for quite a long time now. So let&amp;rsquo;s hop in and start reading!
Let&amp;rsquo;s start off with a bit of info about me! I play Roblox, an online gaming platform and I highly enjoy it. Call me weird or cheezy but hey! It&amp;rsquo;s what I enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>/2020/08/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 21:07:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/08/hello/</guid>
      <description>Hi my name is Sneha! This is my brand new blog where I plan on posting&amp;hellip; stuff? I haven&amp;rsquo;t exactly planned everything out but&amp;hellip; hey! The future is later, not now! Anywho, I might write some stories and stuff so yea! Keep on the lookout! I will post everyday&amp;hellip; or least I&amp;rsquo;m planning to! Well, this is all for the opening of my brand new blog site! Now buckle up and enjoy!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>